With the 159th pick, in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Minnesota Vikings select
>> [cheering]
>> I want to take this guy. He's [music] a
He's one of my favorite Wolverines. Just
follow him and you can watch time being
given to potentially his newest
teammate. Not potentially, it is his
newest teammate.
>> [music]
>> Just follow Max Bredeson and you will
score touchdowns. And then [music] he
can work his way out of the backfield,
one of the best H-backs and fullbacks,
two-time captain of [music] the Michigan
Wolverines, just like his brother, Ben,
the only brothers to be two-time
captains in the history of the program.
>> [music]
>> I mean, without him, team 144 would not
have won at all. He is everything. He
does it all, and the Vikings got [music]
themselves a winner.